1	Hair-Do and I will go after the Hot-Air Balloon. You attack.
2	I'll tell you when I see an enemy. Get the Ballista ready!
3	Whatever you do, don't let our Hot-Air Balloon take too much damage.
4	The Ballista takes time to reload. Make those shots count.
5	There's a wyvern off the forward bow! Man the Ballista!
6	Keep that Ballista primed! You'll have a better chance to hit.
7	We've got a few Flints in case of emergency, but use them sparingly.
8	They keep coming!
9	Wyverns incoming!
10	Where are they all coming from?!
11	More incoming. Brace yourselves!
12	More incoming. Brace yourselves!
13	They've gotten above us! I can't see the other balloon.
14	More wyverns coming at us. These might be tough...
15	Take a break on that side. We're in the clear.
16	Don't let your guard down!
17	Look! It's the kidnapper's balloon! After them!
18	Don't let the wyverns distract you. We have to take down that other balloon!
19	More wyverns coming in hot!
20	Argh, we have to faster or we'll lose them!
21	We won't make it at this rate...
22	Darn it. They're coming out of the woodworks.
23	...I don't see the other balloon.
24	I think we lost them.
