0	Let's fight!
1	Uh, I think I've got the wrong person.
2	Haha, nice weather today!
3	You've got a tough face to look at.
4	You can't outwit me. I'm brilliant!
5	It doesn't take much to make me look great!
6	Bartender! Get me a drink! I can't look at this ugly mug sober.
7	The eyepatch is the mark of a great pirate.
8	Watch out! I've got you in my sights.
9	Without confidence, you're nothing.
10	Do ya hear them cheering on their leader? That's me!
11	I could take ya on with a belly full of rum.
12	I could beat you with my eyes closed.
13	You can't think yer a match for me!
14	I may look weak, but I have my tricks!
15	Yer lookin' pretty fluffy, landlubber!
16	You're all looks.
17	I'm faster than the wind.
18	This is where your luck runs out.
19	Yer all talk!
20	Back down now and I won't kill ya.
21	I thought I smelled old cheese...
22	Work hard, and ya might be half as good a pirate as I am.
23	It's time ya got a look at a true pirate.
24	This is easier than shooting minnows with a cannon.
25	My glare is enough to defeat you, guppy!
26	Call my name, and I appear.
27	Lemme show you what fear looks like.
28	I've eaten boogers bigger than you!
29	I'm handsome enough to be famous.
30	I've never lost a fight.
31	There's no pirate braver than I!
32	If I knew they'd let a wimp like you be a pirate, I woulda joined the circus.
33	Ya dance around like a monkey when ya fight!
34	You should go, while I'm feeling merciful.
35	I'll shock ya into submission!
36	Hey, ready to have some fun?
37	Be careful. You don't want to wake the dragon!
38	This'll be over before you can blink.
39	Let me show you my power.
40	I'll show you hell.
41	It's not over until it's over.
42	You'll be spilling tears before you're spilling blood.
43	Aiming for my face? You must be feeling brave.
44	You should feel honored to see me fight.
45	Any last words? My sword would like to hear them.
46	I read your mind. You're terrified!
47	That's not a sword! That's scrap metal!
48	You're not fit to be a first mate!
49	You're already dead.
50	Are my taunts making you hot under the collar?
51	Temp 51
52	Temp 53
53	Temp 54
54	Temp 55
55	Temp 56
56	Temp 57
57	Temp 58
58	Temp 59
59	Temp 60
60	Go away before I mop the floor with you.
61	Hmph. You got lucky!
62	What?
63	I know. It's difficult to confront such beauty every day.
64	So is a lightbulb, but I turn those off all the time.
65	You're right. Just put a bag over your head. Much better!
66	Is that what you say into the mirror every morning?
67	The only pirates that wear eyepatches are the slow ones.
68	Lucky me. You're blind as an angler fish!
69	I'm confident that I am something.
70	Laughing at you isn't the same thing as cheering.
71	Looks like you've already had a few too many bellyfuls of rum as it is.
72	Let's test that out. I have a blindfold right here.
73	I know you're a little below my level, but I'm willing to let you try.
74	Tricks are for kids! Strength is all that matters.
75	I'm perfect just the way I am!
76	You're all ugly.
77	More like a gentle breeze.
78	That's not what me rabbit's foot says!
79	And yer all stupid!
80	I never back down.
81	That was just your breath. You should brush your teeth.
82	How much is half of not very good?
83	Oh yeah? Where is he?
84	Everything is easier than that. Minnows are small and difficult to hit!
85	Is that a glare? Your eyes are barely open!
86	Sillyface McPoopdeck, I summon thee!
87	No need. I got a good look the moment you decided to fight me.
88	You eat boogers? Gross!
89	If only you didn't have that rotten personality.
90	There's a first time for everything!
91	That's because brave pirates don't live long.
92	It's a shame. You've really got the face to be a clown.
93	That never stopped the Monkey King!
94	Mercy's just another word for chicken.
95	Try it. I'm wearing rubber boots.
96	I came for a fight. Have fun on your own time!
97	Dragon? More like a salamander.
98	I just blinked. Look, I did it again.
99	I've got more power than you in my pinky finger!
100	You did that when you opened your mouth.
101	It's over when I say it's over.
102	I'll be spilling my lunch if you keep using those cheesy lines.
103	I was just trying to fix it up. It's a mess!
104	I feel a lot of revulsion right now. Is that close enough?
105	You're an idiot. Swords don't have ears.
106	What am I thinking now, then? Hint: it's about how dumb you sound.
107	Really? I got it from your bag.
108	I know. I should be a captain!
109	What are you? The fist of the wimp star?
110	Not at all. I'm cooler than a sea cucumber.
111	_Temp51
112	_Temp52
113	Argh...
114	Ack! I-I can't...
115	Ugh, I can't fall now!
116	I can't believe this!
117	That attack!
118	You're quite strong.
119	Ya got me, but I'm not givin' up!
120	Calico Jack
121	Flail
122	Barbados
123	Blackbeard
124	Black Bart
125	El Draco
126	I'd better show you what's up.
127	How about a drink?
128	D-do you need something?
129	I used to be the boss in my town! Wanna get a taste?
130	Huh? You must be out of your mind.
131	What sort of insignificant flea are you?
132	Yeah, get outta here.
133	Hic! I'mma little drunk...
134	Oh well, stuff happens, ya know?
135	You make it so easy for me.
136	Stop bugging me.
137	Go away.
138	Have mercy!
139	Nooo!
140	I don't have the will to go on.
141	Please forgive me!
142	Ahhhhh!
143	I-I'm scared...
144	ARGHHHHHH! Do-over! I demand a do-over!
