0	Sharp teeth from mutant animals were found near Ciar Dungeon.
1	You secured testimony that the Apostle's wings were seen in the northern pasture.
2	You retrieved damaged Light Armor and Broadswords and asked Ferghus to repair them.
3	Northwest of Dugald Aisle seems to be the most probable place.
4	You delivered the supplies from Manus to the injured.
5	You collected parts of the log while chasing after the Mage.
6	You finished reading the manuscript.
7	You secured testimony that the farmer's livestock has disappeared.
8	You retrieved the Magic Tool without being seen by the residents.
9	Someone suspicious was spotted in a pub in Bangor.
10	You got Holy Water of Lymilark from the stock in the Tara Healer's House.
11	You healed the injured knights.
12	The stolen Topaz was traced to Rabbie Dungeon.
13	Footprints and a piece of a mysterious note were found around the Dragon Ruins. They look like traces of the Apostles.
14	You learned about herbalism from Manus for effective injury treatment.
15	According to Duncan, suspicious experiments are taking place around the graveyard.
16	You created a storage closet with drawers.
17	You discovered something from the message the girl left behind.
18	You witnessed one of the Tir Chonaill residents receiving something from a man wearing a bandanna.
19	Training went as planned.
20	You gave the trackers from Belvast the slip.
21	Prophets were found in Fiodh Forest at dawn, poaching subjects for their experiments.
22	According to Endelyon, some merchants that frequent Tir Chonaill have spoken ill of the Churches of Lymilark.
23	You found evidence of the experiments on living bodies near Barri Dungeon.
24	You tracked down and rescued an Eiler unit member.
25	You requested additional military support.
26	All areas of Dugald Aisle have been patrolled.
27	You were able to launch a surprise attack, but you encountered no Prophets.
28	You tamed the wild horse.
29	You learned how to hunt the mutant animals more effectively.
30	You convinced Lassar to return to Tir Chonaill right before arriving at the ruins.
31	You destroyed the altar.
32	You decoded the message and discovered a new order, 'Emergency, lack of subjects for experiment'.
33	You found that parts were missing in the log from the old woman near Sen Mag Plains.
34	The blonde girl couldn't remember much, but grew scared when the name Pennar was mentioned.
35	You restored the Prophet's artifact.
36	You found the cargo along the shore.
37	You learned how to fight the mutant monsters more effectively.
38	After giving useful herbs to the old woman, she explained that she found the log near the excavation site in Bangor.
39	You witnessed someone secretly speaking about a document in the pub in Bangor.
40	You found a shining diamond near Karu Forest.
41	You found a leaf that only grows in Corrib Valley on the mutant animal's corpse.
42	You found base herbs, antidote herbs, and water.
43	After checking the handwriting, the letter was determined to be from a man in Emain Macha.
44	You eliminated Kobold Bandits and retrieved the stolen goods.
45	The supply unit arrived safely in Tara.
46	You rescued the patrolman from the mutant monsters near Taillteann Beacon Mound.
47	You restored the graveyard and played music to comfort the injured souls.
48	You mopped up the bandits and retrieved the supplies.
49	You eliminated mutant monsters near Taillteann Farm.
50	You rescued some residents in the storage.
51	You got some clues from talking to Ethna.
52	You repaired the equipment.
53	You collected samples from the mutant monsters.
54	You delivered the remedy potions to injured knights in Karu Forest.
55	You cleared out the mutant monsters around Abb Neagh Lake.
56	You collected leather for light armor.
57	You asked an Alchemist to drop the temperature of the swarming lake.
58	You recovered parts of the lost memories.
59	You performed the ancient ritual by dodging the Prophet's attacks and eliminating evil spirits, all to protect Cor Village.
60	You obtained testimony that rats started to rage after the events at Emain Macha Lake.
61	You eliminated the mutant rats.
62	You eliminated the Mutant Stone Gargoyle.
63	A shadow suspected to be a Prophet was spotted near the Assembly Area.
64	You acquired five special Arat Berries.
65	You protected the river from being further contaminated by removing the mutant monster.
66	You protected the Crusaders until they recovered.
67	You collected clues to uncover the Prophet's identity.
87	There was no special information.
88	There was nothing special. I bet you had to pull a few strings for this, right? Thank you so much, captain.
89	Thank you, captain!
90	There's nothing to report... By the way, thank you, captain!
91	Back then, I didn't know that there were stories kept secret from me. I... now realize that I never really understood my father.
92	The first mission was successful.
93	The first mission was successful.
94	I've acquired the Medal of Victory!
95	I've brought back the Medal of Dignity you asked for. It wasn't too difficult.
96	I... I brought back the Medal of Will.
97	I've acquired the Medal of Wisdom as you ordered.
98	I've acquired the Medal of Protection. Are you set now?
99	This is it, right? Medal of Honor? Ha ha! It was a piece of cake!
100	All dungeons around Tir Chonaill were checked, but no pollutant was found.
101	You couldn't collect testimonies about the rumor.
102	You failed to find the remaining equipment.
103	You didn't find any places where Apostles appear.
104	In the middle of the delivery, suspicious robed figures stole the supplies.
105	You failed to pursue the Mage.
106	You couldn't finish reading the manuscript.
107	There were no witnesses.
108	You weren't able to retrieve the Magic Tool.
109	You couldn't find the Mad Seer's altar.
110	You didn't obtain enough Holy Water of Lymilark.
111	You failed to heal the injured knights. Their injuries grew worse.
112	Digo's ledger had no record of a suspicious trader that headed to Dunbarton.
113	There was nothing suspicious around Bangor.
114	You didn't learn anything about herbalism from Manus.
115	There was nothing special recently.
116	You failed to create a storage closet.
117	You failed to decode the girl's message.
118	There was nothing suspicious.
119	Additional training failed.
120	You couldn't slip away from the trackers at Belvast.
121	There were no suspicious intruders.
122	No villagers spoke of suspicious outsiders.
123	You found no evidence of the experiment.
124	You couldn't find traces of the Eiler unit member.
125	You failed to request military support.
126	You didn't have enough time to patrol everywhere.
127	You failed to find the secret location.
128	You couldn't tame the wild horse.
129	You couldn't learn how to hunt the mutant animals effectively.
130	You warned Lassar, but couldn't stop her from heading to the ruins.
131	You failed to find the altar.
132	You failed to decode the message.
133	You surveyed all parts of Bangor, but couldn't find the original log.
134	The blonde girl couldn't remember what happened to her while she was missing.
135	You failed to restore the Prophet's artifact.
136	You failed to recover the cargo from the shore.
137	You couldn't learn how to fight the mutant monsters effectively.
138	The old woman refused to talk.
139	You hid in the pub in Bangor, but there was no one preaching.
140	You failed to find a shining diamond.
141	You checked the corpse, but found no special clues.
142	You found base herbs and antidote herbs, but failed to find water.
143	You failed to find the writer of the letter.
144	You failed to eliminate the Kobold Bandits.
145	The supply unit was plundered and couldn't make it to Tara.
146	You couldn't find the patrolman in Taillteann.
147	You failed to restore the graveyard.
148	You mopped up the bandits but failed to retrieve the supplies.
149	You failed to eliminate the mutant monsters near Taillteann Farm.
150	The residents were taken by the Prophets before you could rescue them.
151	You talked to Ethna, but failed to gather any clues.
152	You failed to repair the equipment. They're far too broken to use.
153	You failed to collect mutant samples.
154	You failed to find the injured knights in Karu Forest.
155	You failed to eliminate all of the mutant monsters around Abb Neagh Lake.
156	You couldn't collect leather for light armor.
157	You couldn't check on Emain Macha Lake.
158	You failed to recover any of the lost memories.
159	The Prophets interrupted the ancient ritual.
160	You eliminated some of the rats, but couldn't uncover the reason behind their rise.
161	You failed to eliminate the mutant rats.
162	You couldn't eliminate the Mutant Stone Gargoyle.
163	You found no one near the Assembly Area.
164	You couldn't acquire the special Arat Berries.
165	Due to the strong currents, you couldn't get the monster out of the river.
166	The Apostle attacked before the Crusaders could recover.
167	You couldn't find any clues to the Prophet's identity.
187	You couldn't find the informant.
188	Due to bad weather, I wasn't able to reach my destination.
189	They were all out of strawberry milk... And told me to come back later... *Sob*
190	I... I wasn't able to get what I wanted.
191	I wasn't able to get the information I wanted.
192	I'm sorry. I failed the mission.
193	I'm sorry. I failed the mission.
194	Hrng, I'm sorry. I couldn't get the Medal of Victory.
195	I couldn't get hold of the Medal of Dignity.\nI-I make mistakes too, you know!
197	I'm sorry. I couldn't get ahold of the Medal of Wisdom.
199	Oh! I'm sorry... I couldn't get the Medal of Honor.\nShucks... Maybe I should've listened to Kaour and trained harder.
200	You transported the Special Supply Box.
201	You transported the Special Supply Box.
202	You transported the Special Supply Box.
203	You transported the Special Supply Box.
204	You transported the Special Supply Box.
205	You transported the Special Supply Box.
206	You transported the Special Supply Box.
207	You transported the Special Supply Box.
208	You transported the Special Supply Box.
209	You transported the Special Supply Box.
210	You transported the Special Supply Box.
211	You transported the Special Supply Box.
212	You transported the Special Supply Box.
213	You transported the Special Supply Box.
214	You transported the Special Supply Box.
215	You transported the Special Supply Box.
216	You transported the Special Supply Box.
217	You transported the Special Supply Box.
218	You transported the Special Supply Box.
219	You couldn't transport the Special Supply Box.
220	You couldn't transport the Special Supply Box.
221	You couldn't transport the Special Supply Box.
222	You couldn't transport the Special Supply Box.
223	You couldn't transport the Special Supply Box.
224	You couldn't transport the Special Supply Box.
225	You couldn't transport the Special Supply Box.
226	You couldn't transport the Special Supply Box.
227	You couldn't transport the Special Supply Box.
228	You couldn't transport the Special Supply Box.
229	You couldn't transport the Special Supply Box.
230	You couldn't transport the Special Supply Box.
231	You couldn't transport the Special Supply Box.
232	You couldn't transport the Special Supply Box.
233	You couldn't transport the Special Supply Box.
234	You couldn't transport the Special Supply Box.
235	You couldn't transport the Special Supply Box.
236	You couldn't transport the Special Supply Box.
237	You couldn't transport the Special Supply Box.
238	I couldn't get the Medal of Protection.\nI won't make excuses. I apologize for my lack of skills.
239	I'm sorry. I couldn't acquire the Medal of Will. I was so scared...
