0	Wanna play Rock Paper Scissors?
1	Let's do this fair and square!
2	Let's just have fun.
3	I've got a good feeling...
4	I know I'm going to win, but let's have a good match.
5	I think I'll be winning again this time.
6	Now now, don't go crying when you lose.
7	Oh come on, let me win once!
8	I'm going to use Rock, so you should use Scissors, okay?
9	You are way too predictable.
10	Nice! I'm on a streak today.
11	Hooray! I won!
12	I can't believe I lost...
13	Man, this just isn't my day...
14	Rock Paper Scissors time!
15	Try to beat me if you can.
16	Go easy on me, please.
17	Focus!
18	Bring it!
19	Heeheeheehee!
20	What now? WHAT NOW?!
21	Aw, shucks.
22	I lost? What?!
23	NOOOOOO!
